albanza.com 2004-06-07

# HOSTARS - Privacy

## Privacy Information

**HOSTARS** \- is providing this privacy statement to make you aware of HOSTARS's practices and procedures regarding the ways HOSTARS collects and processes information submitted and/or collected on HOSTARS web site(s).

**What type of information does HOSTARS collect?**

**HOSTARS** does not collect personal information on HOSTARS web sites unless you choose to provide personal information to HOSTARS. On selected HOSTARS web sites, you can order product or services. In order to process these orders, HOSTARS will collect your name, billing information, transaction and credit card information.

**Information Collection and Third Parties**

**HOSTARS** will not collect personal information when you visit HOSTARS's (or HOSTARS third party providers) web sites unless you choose to provide such personal information. HOSTARS does collect certain information, including Internet Protocol addresses, Internet domain names, the web browser and operating system used to access the HOSTARS web site(s), the files visited, the time spent in each file, and the time and date of each visit. HOSTARS may use a third party ad server advertisements or other third parties to provide content on behalf of HOSTARS. 

**HOSTARS** also utilizes cookies in conjunction with its web sites or advertisements (collectively for purposes of this paragraph "web sites"). Generally, cookies are identifiers that can be sent from a web site via your browser to be placed on your computers hard drive. Thereafter when you visit a web site, a message is sent back to the web server by the browser accessing the web site. You may elect not to accept cookies by changing the designated settings on your web browser. However, not utilizing cookies may prevent you from using certain functions and features of web sites. The information collected from the use of cookies is used and analyzed to improve HOSTARS's web sites.
